Contact

molly.bennetts@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/molly-bennett-bsn-rn-65055145 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

communication numeracy presentation

Languages

French (Limited Working)

Certifications

BLS

Honors-Awards

University's Academic Excellence Award

University Scholar

Molly Bennett, BSN RN

Travel Nurse at Accountable Healthcare Staffing Greater Boston Area

Summary

Registered Nurse with over 3 years of critical care experience with specialized practice in Medical/Surgical ICU. Experienced in providing multifaceted healthcare to a diverse group of patient population to include oncology, ICCU, step-down units, PACU and medical surgical nursing.

Experience

South Shore Health Travel Nurse December 2019 - Present (7 months) Massachusetts, United States

Dartmouth-Hitchcock

5 years

Registered Nurse

July 2015 - Present (5 years)

New Hamshire

Medical Hematology Oncology

- Assessed patients' physical condition and created and implemented care programs accordingly.
- Respond to changes in a patient's condition quickly and appropriately, immediately delivering nursing and/or physician driven interventions while maintaining a calm, safe environment for the patient.
- Provide nursing care that is patient and family centered by collaborating with other health care professionals, educators, clients and their families to achieve optimal wellness outcomes.
- Provide concise, detailed documentation of pertinent physical assessment findings and other nursing problems in the patient's medical record.

December 2016 - December 2019 (3 years 1 month)

• Float to acute healthcare facilities and other units throughout DHMC including Medical/Surgical ICU, and Step-Down Units as needed.

Massachusetts General Hospital Travel Registered Nurse February 2019 - December 2019 (11 months) Boston, Massachusetts

MICU/SICU patients

St. Elizabeth's Medical Center ICU Registered Nurse December 2018 - March 2019 (4 months) Boston, Massachusetts

Mixed unit ICU including cardiac ICU, MICU, SICU

Alice Peck Day Health Systems, Corp. Registered Nurse December 2015 - November 2016 (1 year) Lebanon nh

Washington County Mental Health Services Counselor June 2014 - June 2015 (1 year 1 month) vermont

- Monitored the condition and behavior of client and accurately assessed stability.
- Utilized a recovery model, provided supportive counseling and constructive interactions to promote consumer emotional stability and increase clients ability to problem solve.
- Participated in treatment planning; write treatment plans based on input from the team and consumer; implemented and revised treatment plans, tailoring goals and objectives to meet the clients needs.

Dartmouth-Hitchcock Student Nurse-Practicum January 2015 - March 2015 (3 months) Lebanon NH

Completed 168 hours of medical surgical nursing at Dartmouth Hitchcock Medical Center on the Medical Hematology Oncology Unit. Under the supervision of a preceptor I worked to provide care to patients with varying types of cancer.

Four Seasons Care Home Med-Tech January 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 8 months) vermont

- Distributed medications and provide treatments according to physician's orders and in accordance with facility policy; responsible for knowing the purpose, usual dose range, monitoring requirements, effects, and potential adverse reaction of drugs administered prior to administration
- Obtained and recorded patients' vital signs, intake and output and blood glucose and collects samples for urinalysis and stool samples
- Monitored personal and staff compliance to resident's rights
- reported on status of residents to oncoming staff members

State University of New York Research Assistant August 2009 - May 2010 (10 months)

Analyzed pollen morphology and bee foraging behavior in an Australian eggplant relative. Research performed under Dr. Daniel Vogt and Dr. Christopher Martine. Extracted seeds from dried specimen of Australian plants Solanum Sejunctum and Solanum assymetriphyllum. Analyzed pollen using microscpe and found the species produced inaperturate pollen.

Education

Norwich University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2015)

SUNY Plattsburgh

Bachelor of Science, Biochemistry · (2006 - 2010)